One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Wealth, fame, power...
עושר, תהילה, כוח...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, obtained everything the world has to offer.
גולד רוג'ר, מלך הפיראטים, השיג את כל מה שהיה לעולם להציע.
What he said in his final moments drove countless souls to the seas.
מה שאמר ברגעיו האחרונים דחף אינספור נשמות להפליג באוקינוס.
You want my treasure?
רוצים את האוצר שלי?
Go ahead.
קדימה.
Find it!
מצאו אותו!
Everything is right where I left it!
הכל נמצא היכן שהשארתי אותו!
People set their sights on the Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams.
עינהם של האנשים נישאו אל הקו הגדול במרדף אחר החלומות שלהם.
The world has truly entered the Great Pirate Era!
העולם אכן נכנס לעידן הפיראטים הגדול!
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams
Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
One Piece! ONE PIECE
One Piece! ONE PIECE
Compasses? Not for me. Left them all behind Rashinban nante juutai no moto
Compasses? Not for me. Left them all behind Rashinban nante juutai no moto
I'm headed out to sea, with my heart serving as guide Netsu ni ukasare kaji wo toru no sa
I'm headed out to sea, with my heart serving as guide Netsu ni ukasare kaji wo toru no sa
Following the ancient map to the spot marked "X" reveals Hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
Following the ancient map to the spot marked "X" reveals Hokori kabutteta takara no chizu mo
Yeah, it's only legendary till someone proves it's real Tashikameta no nara densetsu janai!
Yeah, it's only legendary till someone proves it's real Tashikameta no nara densetsu janai!
When the world's got you down,
When the world's got you down,
Kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
Kojin teki na arashi wa dare ka no
lean on your crew, they'll turn it around
lean on your crew, they'll turn it around
Their biorhythm will carry you through BIORHYTHM nokkatte
Their biorhythm will carry you through BIORHYTHM nokkatte
We're gonna make the most of it Omoi sugoseba ii!
We're gonna make the most of it Omoi sugoseba ii!
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
Come aboard and bring along all your hopes and dreams Arittake no yume wo kaki atsume
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
I know together we'll find everything we're looking for Sagashi mono wo sagashi ni yuku no sa
Got some change to my name, POCKET no COIN
Got some change to my name, POCKET no COIN
and maybe you wanna be my friend? Soreto YOU WANNA BE MY FRIEND?
and maybe you wanna be my friend? Soreto YOU WANNA BE MY FRIEND?
We are, we are on the cruise! WE ARE, WE ARE ON THE CRUISE!
We are, we are on the cruise! WE ARE, WE ARE ON THE CRUISE!
WE ARE!
WE ARE!
For Whom the Bell Tolls
למי צלצלו הפעמונים
H-He just...
ה-הוא...
He broke Captain Kuro's cat claw!
הוא שבר את הטפרים של קפטן קורו!
Only five of these weird sword things left!
נשארו רק חמישה מהחרבות המוזרות שלך!
It's okay! He has plenty of fight left in him!
זה בסדר! הוא עדיין רחוק מלהכנע!
Yeah! He's still got the other claw!
כן! נשארו לו הטפרים ביד השניה!
Scratch him up and kill him, Captain Kuro!
שרוט ותהרוג אותו, קפטן קורו!
Whoa, you can't call him that anymore!
וואה, אתה לא יכול לקרוא לו ככה יותר!
Oh yeah... I think his name in the village was Klaha... something...
הו כן... נראה לי שהשם החדש שלו היה קלה... משהו...
Mr. Klah, then!
שיהיה, אדון קלה!
– Mr. Klah! Get 'im!
– תפוס אותו, אדון קלה!
Would you all just...
אולי פשוט...
shut the hell up?!
תסתמו את הפה?!
Come on out, you twerps!
צאו החוצה, פרעושים!
I know you're hiding in there!
אני יודע שאתם מתחבאים שם!
Give it up already!
וותרו כבר!
Come over here!
בוא לכאן!
We'll take you straight to her!
ניקח אותך אליה!
You really think I'm that gullible? As if I'd trust anything you brats say!
נראה לכם שאני כזה תמים? כאילו שאאמין לשקרים שלכם!
Huh?!
הא?!
We got him!
תפסנו אותו!
Now!
עכשיו!
Take this!
קח את זה!
Pepper Attack!
מתקפת פלפל!
– Push!
– דחפו!
Owww!
אוץ'!
Ow! Ow!
או! או!
– It's over, hypnotist!
– אתה גמור, מהפנט!
Don't get cocky.
אל תתלהבו יותר מידי.
Darn it! We failed...!
לעזאזל! נכשלנו...!
You've made a mockery of me.
עשיתם ממני צחוק.
But I am still a pirate...
אבל אני עדיין פיראט...
– Onion!
– בצל!
You wannabe pirate brats poked your noses in a bit too deep...
פרחחים פיראטים בכאילו, דחפתם את האף למקומות שלא צריך...
Where are you hiding, Miss?!
איפה את מתחבאת, גברת?!
I'll start by executing these three.
אתחיל בלהרוג את השלושה האלו...
You can reflect on your poor choice to meddle with real pirates...
תוכלו לחשוב על הבחירה העגומה שלכם להתערב בעסקים של פיראטים...
on your way to the afterlife.
בדרך לעולם הבא.
There you are.
הנה את.
No!
לא!
Run, Miss Kaya!
רוצי, גברת קאיה!
Hey!
היי!
Yeah! That's them!
כן! אלו הם!
It's the other way?!
הם מהצד השני?!
I'll eliminate each and every one of you later...
אחסל כל אחד ואחד מכם אחר כך...
That includes Jango!
כולל את ג'אנגו!
Wh-Why us?!
ל-למה אותנו?!
Please stop joking around, Captain Kuro!
בבקשה תפסיק עם השטויות, קפטן קורו!
It's still not too late for us to attack the village, right?!
לא מאוחר מידי בשביל שנתקוף את הכפר, נכון?!
And if Captain Jango gets her to write her will, your plan will succeed!
ואם קפטן ג'אנגו יגרום לה לכתוב את הצוואה, התוכנית עדיין תעבוד!
Do not concern yourselves with the details of my plan...
אתם לא צריכים לדאוג לגבי התוכנית שלי...
All I need from you are corpses on which to pin the blame.
כל מה שאני צריך מכם אלו גופות שאוכל להאשים.
I never intended to let any of you leave this village alive.
מלכתחילה לא תכננתי שתעזבו את הכפר הזה בחיים.
I can't let anyone who knows my true identity live.
אני לא יכול לתת לאף אחד שיודע את הזהות שלי לחיות.
No way...
אין מצב...
Then you planned to kill us from the very start?!
אז תכננת להרוג אותנו מההתחלה?!
That's right...
בדיוק...
For three long years now, back when I was still going by Captain Kuro...
במשך שלוש שנים, מאז שעדיין הייתי ידוע בשם קפטן קורו...
it was all...
הכל היה...
it was all part of my plan!
הכל היה חלק מהתוכנית!
Man, you guys are dumb.
בחיי, כולכם מטומטמים.
Your pirate crew is so lame!
אתם צוות פיראטים מאעפן!
"Lame"?
"מאעפן"?
In the end, a pirate crew is nothing but a pack of stray dogs!
בסופו של דבר צוות פיראטים הם לא יותר מאסופה של כלבים נטושים!
What could they possibly accomplish without a plan?!
מה הם מסוגלים לעשות בלי תוכנית?!
Every last one should just shut up and follow my orders!
כולם צריכים פשוט לסתום ולעקוב אחרי התוכניות שלי!
Crew members are a captain's loyal pawns!
חברי צוות הם פיסות משחק נאמנות לקפטן!
I'm the one who decides whether to kill them or spare them.
אני מחליט אם להרוג אותם או לחוס עליהם!
No matter how great the obstacle, they simply need to stand up to it...
לא משנה כמה גדול המכשול, הם פשוט צריכים להתמודד...
and die according to my plans.
ולמות בהתאם לתוכניות שלי.
This is what it means to be a pirate!
זו המשמעות של להיות פיראט!
Don't patronize me, you little vagrant!
שלא תעז לשפוט אותי, פרחח נודד אחד!
Even if a captain like you...
אפילו אם היו לך...
had hundreds or thousands of men following him...
מאות אלפים של אנשים שמקשיבים לך...
you'd never be better than Usopp!
עדיין לא היית מוצלח יותר מאוסופ!
What?!
מה?!
You're saying I'm inferior to a kid pretending to be a pirate captain?
אתה רומז לזה שאני פחות מוצלח מילד שמעמיד פנים שהוא קפטן פיראטים?
That's right!
נכון מאוד!
How droll!
כמה מגוכח!
Don't get cocky just because you snapped one of my claws!
אל תתנשא רק בגלל ששברת את הטפרים ביד אחת שלי!
How exactly is he better than me?!
איך בדיוק הוא טוב ממני?!
Let's hear it!
בוא נשמע!
Character.
אופי.
What?!
מה?!
You have no idea what it means to be a pirate!
אין לך מושג מה זה אומר להיות פיראט!
H-He...
ה-הוא...
He kept up with the Pussyfoot Maneuver!
הוא שוב הולך על טפיפות החתול!
How insulting...
כמה מעליב...
If you're curious about real pirates, then allow me to demonstrate...
אם אתה רוצה לדעת על פיראטים אמיתיים,  אז הרשה לי להראות לך...
true terror.
אימה אמיתית.
The terror of a pirate who has faced death countless times!
האימה של פיראט שהביט למוות בעיניים אינספור פעמים!
Hey! That stance! Is he...?!
היי! העמדה הזו! הוא...?!
That's the move he's gonna use?!
הזה?! הוא הולך להשתמש במהלך
But he's only fighting one guy!
אבל הוא נלחם רק בבחור אחד!
But that's definitely it!
אבל זה ללא ספק המהלך!
He's planning to use Whole Nine Yarns!
הוא הולך להשתמש במהלך תשע הנשמות!
Aren't we in danger here?!
זה לא אומר שאנחנו בסכנה כאן?!
He'll get us, too!
הוא יחסל גם אותנו!
He already plans to kill us!
הוא ממילא תכנן לחסל אותנו!
He even said so earlier!
הוא אפילו אמר זאת קודם!
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
בבקשה תפסיק, קפטן קורו!
Anything but that!
הכל, רק לא זה!
We'll do anything you want!
נעשה כל מה שתרצה!
Please, Captain Kuro!
בבקשה, קפטן קורו!
What's the big deal?
מה הקטע?
He's just swaying back and forth...
הוא רק מתנדנד קדימה ואחורה...
– Please stop, Captain Kuro!
– בבקשה מספיק, קפטן קורו!
Whole Nine Yarns!
תשע הנשמות!
What a pitiful haul...
איזה שלל אומלל...
I thought they'd have a little more treasure than that...
הייתי בטוחה שיהיו להם יותר אוצרות...
Let's see, is the fight over yet?
בואו נראה, הקרב כבר נגמר?
What?
מה?
Nobody's moving...
אף אחד לא זז...
Is it over?
זה נגמר?
There it is!
הנה זה!
Wh-Why's he over there?!
ל-למה הוא שם?!
Not again!
לא שוב!
Now it's the wall!
עכשיו זה הקיר!
Please stop, Captain Kuro!
בבקשה תעצור, קפטן קורו!
It's no use! His Pussyfoot Maneuver attacks are out of control!
אין טעם, טפיפות החתול שלו יצאו מכלל שליטה!
He's moving so fast he doesn't even know what he's slashing!
הוא זז כל כך מהר שהוא לא יודע מי הוא משסף!
He's already cut down so many of our cr–
הוא חתך כבר כל כך הרבה מהצוות שלנ-
Hey!
היי!
Wh-What's happening?!
מ-מה קורה?!
They're getting all sliced up out of nowhere!
הם נחתכים לחתיכות משום מקום!
Show yourself...
תראה את עצמך...
butler...
משרת...
Don't you care about your crew at all?!
לא איכפת לך בכלל מהצוות שלך?!
Luffy...
לופי...
Found you!
מצאתי אותך!
Sly bastard!
ממזר ערמומי!
You should've let me cut you down like a good little boy!
היית צריך לתת לי לחתוך אותך כמו ילד טוב!
Look!
תראה!
My poor men are suffering dearly, and it's all thanks to you!
הצוות המסכן שלי סובלים כל כך, וזה הכל הודות לך!
It would've been kinder if you'd just let my attack kill them!
היה אדיב מצדך אם היית נותן לי לחסל אותם!
Now what?
מה עכשיו?
You look like you have something to say...
נראה שיש לך משהו להגיד...
Yeah...
כן...
No matter what...
לא משנה מה...
I will never be like you.
לעולם לא אהיה כמוך.
Never will...?
לעולם לא תהיה...?
More like never can. Not someone like you, anyway.
זה כי אתה לא מסוגל. זה בלתי אפשרי למישהו כמוך.
Though it doesn't matter...
לא שזה משנה...
since you're going to die here anyway.
כי אתה הולך למות פה בכל מקרה.
Please stop this!
בבקשה, מספיק עם זה!
Leave them alone!
עזוב אותם!
I'll write the will!
אני אכתוב את הצוואה!
N-No!
ל-לא!
They'll kill you if you write it, Miss Kaya!
תיהרגי אם תכתבי אותה, גברת קאיה!
You've got the wrong idea. There are no negotiations to be had here.
התבלבלת. אין פה משא ומתן מלכתחילה.
Captain Kuro told me to get rid of everyone.
קפטן קורו אמר לי להפטר מכולם.
You can't be serious!
אתה לא רציני!
Do as I say, or I'll take my own life!
תעשה מה שאני אומרת, או שאתאבד!
That means no will!
בלי שום צוואה!
Wh-Wh-Whoa! Just hold on!
ו-ו-וואה! רק רגע אחד!
Don't be hasty!
אל תהיי פזיזה!
I absolutely must get you to write that will!
אני מוכרח לגרום לך לכתוב את הצוואה!
M-Miss Kaya!
ג-גברת קאיה!
Fine! The twerps can go!
בסדר! אתן לפרעושים ללכת!
Though they're really in no condition to run...
למרות שהם לא ממש מסוגלים לרוץ...
Sign it, too!
תחתמי!
I know...
אני יודעת...
"I leave my entire estate to my butler, Klahadore..."
"אני משאירה את כל הממון והרכוש שלי למשרת, קלהדור..."
Excellent!
מושלם!
This is your will, all right!
זו בהחלט צוואה מוצלחת!
And I didn't even have to hypnotize you!
אפילו לא הייתי צריך להפנט אותך!
You promise not to kill them, right?
הבטחת לא להרוג אותם, נכון?
Don't worry.
אל תדאגי.
I might not look like it, but I'm a man of my word.
אני אולי לא נראה ככה, אבל מילה שלי היא מילה.
– Miss Kaya!
– גברת קאיה!
There they are!
הנה הם!
There they are! There they are! Stop!
הנה הם! הנה הם! עצור!
Owww! Ow, ow, ow!
אוו! או, או, או!
That's where I got cut, you know!
נחתכתי שם!
Over there!
שם!
Alright, I'll be back!
בסדר, עוד מעט חוזר!
Hey!
היי!
That's far enough, hypno-freak!
זה מספיק, פריק-היפנוזה!
He came after me?!
הוא בא אחרי?!
Guess I'd better finish this quickly!
נראה שאני צריך לסיים את זה מהר!
Everything before now was just an appetizer.
הכל עד עכשיו היה מתאבנים.
You get the three-course treatment.
תקבל את המנה העיקרית.
I will baste you in terror and serve you meticulously on a platter!
אשרה אותך באימה ואגיש אותך על מגש כסף!
Whole Nine Yarns!
תשע הנשמות!
Just try that foot technique now!
נסה את המהלך הזה עכשיו!
Curses! Get off of me!
לעזאזל! רד ממני!
Now your three-year plan is a complete failure!
עכשיו התוכנית בת שלוש השנים שלך היא כשלון!
What?!
מה?!
He caught Captain Kuro!
הוא תפס את קפטן קורו!
Hey, if he wins, that means we won't get killed, right?!
היי, אם הוא ינצח, זה אומר שלא יהרגו אותנו, נכון?!
Now you die!
עכשיו תמותי!
Oh, no, you don't!
הו, לא, אתה לא!
You damn kids!
ילדים ממזרים!
You're just one step too late, bellyband!
נראה שאיחרת בכמה רגעים, רצועת בטן!
You sure about that?
בטוח לגבי זה?
Yes! That branch was in the way!
מושלם! הענף הזה היה בדרך!
What?!
מה?!
Usopp...
אוסופ...
– Captain!
– קפטן!
Eat this, hypnotist!
תאכל את זה, מהפנט!
Get 'im, rubber guy!
תראה לו מה זה, בחור גומי!
Kick Captain Kuro's ass!
כסח את קפטן קורו!
Get away!
לך מפה!
You guys don't get to cheer for me!
אין לכם שום זכות לעודד אותי!
Let go!
הנח לי!
Gum-Gum...
גומי-גומי...
Lethal Exploding Star!
כוכב מתפוצץ קטלני!
My plan...
התוכנית שלי...
...Bell!
...פעמון!
My plan cannot fail!
התוכנית שלי לא יכולה להכשל!